Hello everyone welcome back to Automobile Dekho
channel I am your host R Kumar so in today's
video I will tell you that if
your wingsil is cracked then how
can you take it under claim even if your
insurance is not zero depth so now
you can see that the wingsil of my car is
brand new, it has just been installed
and I have got it installed from my authorized service
center if you don't believe it then for that
I would like to show you something you can
see this
fast tag of my car which is the sticker of the number plate,
this is broken in my hand,
my old one, so I will
show you the number for verification, you
can see a little DLC, you will also see on the number plate,
here you will see a Dell 8
blue so this of my car was broken,
I will tell you how it was broken
[Music] I was
driving towards Jaipur, on the
highway a small stone got stuck
on the windshield of my car, click here,
after that after it got stuck here a small
dot was formed here as if the road was made  Gradually the
line went like this, it reached here, let me
correct it, there were some shortcomings in my car
apart from insurance, I mean I also did
not know that you can do this thing also, my
car is almost 11 years old
and we do not get zero depth insurance in it,
I have purchased comprehensive plan, that is ICC
Lombard, what to do, if your
car's tyre gets broken, it does
not happen accidentally but it happens due to a hit, so
you can get a tyre break due to a hit also,
or your
car is parked on the road,
something fell from a tree, small children threw something,
your tyre can get cracked due to multiple reasons, so
if something like this happens to you
then you do not need to worry about anything, you will get it by
doing simple two steps, of course, the
first thing you have to do is
visit the service center and tell them the reality of how
your tyre got broken, no one has
told you the full story that
brother, there is an accident in Dam or a
SpiceJet, any other reason  You have to tell what has happened to you generally
and apply for a
claim to your insurance company.
I will tell you the documents that will be required from you.
One is your Aadhar card, one is your PAN
card, one is your driving license,
one is RC and along with that a
copy of your insurance. You have to provide all these
documents to your insurance company
and after that you have to proceed
for the claim. After that, in one to
two working days, the
insurance survey will come in your business country, your
vehicle will be inspected and your claim will be
processed. So, I will tell you the things in which you will
not get the insurance of your vehicle.
If someone has
broken the insurance by asking, that is, if
I have broken something in my car myself, then he will
not get it. Now you will say that
brother, how will an insurance company know all this, that
his daily gas is less, it will
not take much time for him to find out,
how will this insurance know that something has
broken by mistake, my car had gone there by mistake.
I was driving on the same road and a small
stone hit me from a truck and it cracked.
If something like this happens to you too or
your car is in the parking lot, children hit it
or nowadays people
play cricket, hair gets lost like cricket,
any exercise date,
if your car breaks due to the action of a third party, then
you can apply
for a claim even in comprehensive plan,
you will have to pay only the filing charges,
which was 1568 something for my car,
so if I talk about the cost of the glass, then it was
6000 something, but
I paid only ₹1500 to
Maruti Suzuki in my authorized dollar, all the rest are
insurance companies, the biggest
question that will come is that brother,
in comprehensive plan, we have 50% tax, when
we purchase insurance, then we are
informed that there will be
50% tax on your car, so how did you complete the claim,
friend, you are adding it, so
gas, if you are zero plane  If you take it then
your car is 100% guaranteed in it, everyone knows this
but in comprehensive plane the
car is 50% guaranteed, in some parts
some of your metal parts are
carried on your car but there is a glass
part which is zero deep and comprehensive
plane, both have 100% guaranteed
because glass part is such a part if
you do even the slightest damage to it,
even a small damage, then the entire
glass part will definitely break, if I
talk about the body or the iron part then you
can read the damage in it, it
depends on the force, brother it will break according to how much force is applied,
but a mirror is such
that whether you apply half force on it or
apply more force, it will definitely break, so
in comprehensive plane also your mirror is 100%
claimed, so in the upcoming
video I will show you that the
wings of your car, these are the parts which have got
their stickers, fast tags,
how can you apply this, fast tag is
enough  It is easy if you are on any fast
or passing near a toll box then
fast ones are available in plenty but
if you want to get such a number plate sticker
replaced then what will you have to do for that
sir, I will tell you the process in the video also
so please make sir and subscribe.